<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gravity Game</string>
    <string name="discordInviteLink" translatable="false">https://discord.gg/H4hFa3vgvZ</string>
    <string name="email" translatable="false">gravitygame2024@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="errorToOpenLink">The link can not be open</string>
    <string name="destroyer">Destroyer</string>
    <string name="ghost">Ghost</string>
    <string name="sumArmy">Total units</string>
    <string name="cruiser">Cruiser</string>
    <string name="chooseArmyTitle">Select units to your army</string>
    <string name="exactArmySize">Select maximum units to your army.</string>
    <string name="warper" translatable="false">Warper</string>
    <string name="nameShip">Unit type</string>
    <string name="enemyShips">Enemy units</string>
    <string name="possibleShipsToMove">Your units</string>
    <string name="shipsToMove">Units on position</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="attack">Attack</string>
    <string name="tinyMapName">Tiny map</string>
    <string name="maxLosses">Max losses</string>
    <string name="nextTurn">Next turn</string>
    <string name="cruiserInfo">Firepower: 1\nHit Points: 10\n\nThe basic unit with no extra ability.</string>
    <string name="destroyerInfo">Firepower: 2\nHit points: 10\n\nThe sum of firepower of all your destroyers is maximally as high as the sum of all enemy ships in the battle.</string>
    <string name="ghostInfo">Firepower: 1\nHit points: 5\n\nEvery ghost in the battle excludes one of the enemy destroyers from battle until the ghost is destroyed.</string>
    <string name="warperInfo">Firepower: 2\nHit points: 1\n\nWarper can move to any sector on a battlefield.</string>
    <string name="titleLostGame">You lost the game</string>
    <string name="titleWinGame">You win the game</string>
    <string name="titleDrawGame">The game is draw</string>
    <string name="lostGame">You have fought hard but unfortunately, the opponent has been more lucky.\nYou lost</string>
    <string name="winGame">You have fought hard and well. The opponent has been destroyed.\nYou win. Congratulation</string>
    <string name="drawGame">You and your opponent have fought hard and there is no winner.</string>
    <string name="battleWithAI">Play against AI</string>
    <string name="infoShipTaskTitle">Display unit info</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="numberOfShipsTaskTitle">Number of units in army</string>
    <string name="closeTutorial">Close tutorial</string>
    <string name="acceptableLossesTitle">Acceptable Losses</string>
    <string name="armyDialogSendShipTitle">Attack with units</string>
    <string name="locationLimitTitle">Limit of units</string>
    <string name="timerTaskTitle">Timer</string>
    <string name="movementTaskTitle">Moving with units</string>
    <string name="locationInfoTitle">Display location</string>
    <string name="locationOwnerTitle">Owner of location</string>
    <string name="infoShipTask">Everywhere in the game, you can tap on a unit name to display information about it.</string>
    <string name="numberShipsTask">Now, you are going to choose units for your army for an incoming battle. There are four units types, but one type is unique and you have one unit of the type in your army by default. You can choose from the remaining three units type to 10 units. It means you will fight with an army containing 11 units. When you select your units hit an OK button.</string>
    <string name="battleOverviewTitle">Battle overview</string>
    <string name="battleOverviewTask">Now, the battle starts. When you play against AI, always play for the blue player starting on the left side of the battle map. There is your home planet, where all your units are located. To win a battle you have to conquer an enemy base on his home planet, which is located on the right side of the battle map. On the contrary, when an opponent conquers your base, you lose the battle.</string>
    <string name="movementTask">To move your units tap on a planet where you have at least one unit and move your finger on a planet you want to move your units. When you tap the planet you move from, planets you can move to will be highlighted by green round. At the beginning of the battle, all planets will be highlighted, because your warper can move everywhere, but the rest of your units can move only to adjustment planets. Try it.</string>
    <string name="sendShipsTask">When you select a planet you move from and a planet you move to, you have to select units that will move. The first column displays enemy units on the planet you want to move to, the second column displays your units able to move in this turn on the planet you select to move from. The last column displays the overall number of units on the planet you move to. It means the last column displays units that are already on the planet plus units you choose to move there. You can\'t move an unlimited number of units on a planet. Every planet has a limit of 6 units.</string>
    <string name="acceptableLossesTask">Aside from selecting units, you can also choose how many units you are willing to sacrifice when a battle with an enemy occurs on the planet. You do that by a slider and the number is a number of units. The battle runs in turns where units are firing at each other with their firepower and the battle ends when one army reaches its acceptable losses. When an army reaches this limit units withdraw from the battle. They stand on the planet and next turn you can choose what to do with them. The battle can end with a draw when both armies reach their acceptable losses at the same time.</string>
    <string name="locationInfoTask">You can also check the details of every planet. You can just tap on the planet to open a table, where the numbers of units in both armies are. You can there also change your acceptable losses on that planet any time you want to.</string>
    <string name="locationOwnerTask">Now you can see planets you move to are marked by flag in you color. It shows the planet is yours, which has impact in battle. When you fight on planet you posses your army has 1 firepower higher.</string>
    <string name="gameRulesTitle">Game rules</string>
    <string name="aboutGameTitle">About game</string>
    <string name="aboutUsTitle">About us</string>
    <string name="settingsTitle">Settings</string>
    <string name="selectLanguage">Select language</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="czech">Czech</string>
    <string name="showTutorial">Show tutorial</string>
    <string name="polish">Polish</string>
    <string name="donate" translatable="false">Donate</string>
    <string name="manyShipsOnBaseLocation">There is too many units on your base planet.</string>
    <string name="statisticTitle">Statistics</string>
    <string name="achievementsTitle" translatable="false">Achievements</string>
    <string name="totalBattle">Total battles: %1$s</string>
    <string name="averageTurns">Average turns: %1$s</string>
    <string name="countOfWins">Count of Wins: %1$s</string>
    <string name="countOfLost">Count of Lost: %1$s</string>
    <string name="countOfDraw">Count of Draws: %1$s</string>
    <string name="date" translatable="false">%1$s</string>
    <string name="battleResult">Result: %1$s</string>
    <string name="turns">Turns: %1$s</string>
    <string name="myShipLost">My units lost: %1$s</string>
    <string name="enemyShipDestroyed">Enemy units destroyed: %1$s</string>
    <string name="generalStatistics">General Statistics</string>
    <string name="detailOfBattle">Detail of Battle</string>
    <string name="enemyShipsBeforeBattle">Enemy units before battle</string>
    <string name="enemyShipsLost">Enemy units lost</string>
    <string name="myShipsBeforeBattle">My units before battle</string>
    <string name="myShipsLost">My units lost</string>
    <string name="battleResultOnLocation">"Last battle on the location you %1$s"</string>
    <string name="battleInfoTask">When a battle occur on a planet, you will see an explosion on it. You can long click on the planet to see, how the battle went.</string>
    <string name="battleInfoTaskTitle">Battle info</string>
    <string name="errorToOpenMail">Your email app cannot be open</string>
</resources>