<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gravity Game</string>
    <string name="discordInviteLink" translatable="false">https://discord.gg/H4hFa3vgvZ</string>
    <string name="buyMeACoffeeLink" translatable="false">https://buymeacoffee.com/gravitygame</string>
    <string name="email" translatable="false">gravitygame2024@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="errorToOpenLink">The link can not be open</string>
    <string name="destroyer">Destroyer</string>
    <string name="ghost">Ghost</string>
    <string name="sumArmy">Total units</string>
    <string name="cruiser">Cruiser</string>
    <string name="chooseArmyTitle">Select units to your army</string>
    <string name="exactArmySize">Select maximum units to your army.</string>
    <string name="warper" translatable="false">Warper</string>
    <string name="nameShip">Unit type</string>
    <string name="enemyShips">Enemy units</string>
    <string name="possibleShipsToMove">Your units</string>
    <string name="shipsToMove">Units on position</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="attack">Attack</string>
    <string name="tinyMapName">Tiny map</string>
    <string name="maxLosses">Max losses</string>
    <string name="nextTurn">Next turn</string>
    <string name="newTurn">NEW TURN</string>
    <string name="cruiserInfo">Firepower: 1\nHit Points: 10\n\nThe basic unit with no extra ability.</string>
    <string name="destroyerInfo">Firepower: 2\nHit points: 10\n\nThe sum of firepower of all your destroyers is maximally as high as the sum of all enemy ships in the battle.</string>
    <string name="ghostInfo">Firepower: 1\nHit points: 5\n\nEvery ghost in the battle excludes one of the enemy destroyers from battle until the ghost is destroyed.</string>
    <string name="warperInfo">Firepower: 2\nHit points: 1\n\nWarper can move to any sector on a battlefield.</string>
    <string name="titleLostGame">You lost the game</string>
    <string name="titleWinGame">You win the game</string>
    <string name="titleDrawGame">The game is draw</string>
    <string name="lostGame">You have fought hard but unfortunately, the opponent has been more lucky.\nYou lost</string>
    <string name="winGame">You have fought hard and well. The opponent has been destroyed.\nYou win. Congratulation</string>
    <string name="drawGame">You and your opponent have fought hard and there is no winner.</string>
    <string name="battleWithAI">Play against AI</string>
    <string name="infoShipTaskTitle">Display unit info</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="numberOfShipsTaskTitle">Number of units in army</string>
    <string name="closeTutorial">Close tutorial</string>
    <string name="acceptableLossesTitle">Acceptable Losses</string>
    <string name="armyDialogSendShipTitle">Attack with units</string>
    <string name="timerTaskTitle">Timer</string>
    <string name="movementTaskTitle">Moving with units</string>
    <string name="locationInfoTitle">Display location</string>
    <string name="locationOwnerTitle">Owner of location</string>
    <string name="infoShipTask">If you want to learn more information about the unit, click on its name.</string>
    <string name="numberShipsTask">For the upcoming battle, you need to select units for your army. There are four types of units. One type is the unique Warper unit, which is assigned to the army by default. Therefore, you need to choose 10 out of the remaining 11 units. Once you have assembled your army, confirm your selection with the button.</string>
    <string name="battleOverviewTitle">Battle overview</string>
    <string name="battleOverviewTask">The battle begins now. If you are playing against AI, your army is blue. Your home planet with a base is on the left side of the battlefield, where your units are also positioned. To win the battle, you must conquer the enemy\’s home planet, which is on the right side of the battlefield. However, if the enemy conquers your home planet, you lose.</string>
    <string name="movementTask">To move your units, place your finger on the planet where you have at least one unit and drag it to the planet you want to move to. When you place your finger on the planet from which you\'re moving and move the finger, all available positions will be marked with a green circle. At the start of the battle, all planets will be marked this way, because the unique Warper unit can move anywhere. However, the remaining types of units can only move to adjacent planets.</string>
    <string name="sendShipsTask">After selecting the movement from one planet to another, you also need to choose the number of units to move. The first column shows the number of enemy units on the selected planet. The second column shows the number of units you can move. The third column shows the total number of units that will be on the selected planet after the move, including both the units that were there from the previous round and the units you\'re moving. There can be no more than 6 units per player on a planet simultaneously.</string>
    <string name="acceptableLossesTask">In addition to selecting units, you must also choose how many units you are willing to sacrifice in the battle. This is done using a slider, and the value represents the number of units. The battle itself takes place in rounds, where the units exchange shots, and it ends when one of the armies reaches its tolerated losses. When an army reaches its maximum tolerated losses, it withdraws from the battle. The withdrawn army remains on the planet, and the player can decide what to do with them in the next turn. The battle can also end in a draw if both armies reach their tolerated losses.</string>
    <string name="locationInfoTask">If you want to view information about a planet, click directly on it. After clicking, you will see the number of units from both armies on the selected planet. In this window, you can also change your tolerated losses at any time.</string>
    <string name="locationOwnerTask">The colour of the flag indicates the owner of the planet. If a blue flag is displayed next to the planet, it is under your control. If a battle takes place on a planet with the colour of your flag, the strength of your army is increased by 1.</string>
    <string name="gameRulesTitle">Game rules</string>
    <string name="aboutGameTitle">About game</string>
    <string name="aboutUsTitle">About us</string>
    <string name="settingsTitle">Settings</string>
    <string name="selectLanguage">Select language</string>
    <string name="english" translatable="false">English</string>
    <string name="czech" translatable="false">Čeština</string>
    <string name="showTutorial">Show tutorial</string>
    <string name="donateTitle" translatable="false">Donate</string>
    <string name="manyShipsOnBaseLocation">There is too many units on your base planet.</string>
    <string name="statisticTitle">Statistics</string>
    <string name="totalBattle">Total battles: %1$s</string>
    <string name="averageTurns">Average turns: %1$s</string>
    <string name="countOfWins">Count of Wins: %1$s</string>
    <string name="countOfLost">Count of Lost: %1$s</string>
    <string name="countOfDraw">Count of Draws: %1$s</string>
    <string name="date" translatable="false">%1$s</string>
    <string name="battleResult">Result: %1$s</string>
    <string name="turns">Turns: %1$s</string>
    <string name="myShipLost">My units lost: %1$s</string>
    <string name="enemyShipDestroyed">Enemy units destroyed: %1$s</string>
    <string name="generalStatistics">General Statistics</string>
    <string name="detailOfBattle">Detail of Battle</string>
    <string name="enemyShipsBeforeBattle">Enemy units before battle</string>
    <string name="enemyShipsLost">Enemy units lost</string>
    <string name="myShipsBeforeBattle">My units before battle</string>
    <string name="myShipsLost">My units lost</string>
    <string name="battleResultOnLocation">"Last battle on the location you have %1$s"</string>
    <string name="winBattleResultForBattleInfo">won</string>
    <string name="lostBattleResultForBattleInfo">lost</string>
    <string name="drawBattleResultForBattleInfo">drew></string>
    <string name="winNominative">Win</string>
    <string name="lostNominative">Lost</string>
    <string name="drawNominative">Draw</string>
    <string name="battleInfoTask">If a battle has taken place on a planet, an explosion symbol will appear on it. You can long-press on such a planet to view information about the battle\'s outcome.</string>
    <string name="battleInfoTaskTitle">Battle info</string>
    <string name="errorToOpenMail">Your email app cannot be open</string>
    <string name="aboutUsText">
        We are two friends united by a love for both board and computer games. Both of us started as young boys with Dungeons &amp; Dragons and later crossed paths in the online strategy game Red Dragon, to which we eventually contributed as creators. Alongside our experience as passionate players, we both developed an interest in going beyond just playing games, exploring how games are created.\n
        Our games usually begin with game mechanics, where we draw inspiration from well-known models but joyfully rewrite or adapt them into original forms. We have high standards for our games and adhere to the principle that players control the game, not the other way around. We avoid methods that unethically compete for your attention.\n\n
        Marek Basovnik\n
        Since childhood, I have been fascinated by puzzles, though I still can\’t solve a Rubik\’s Cube—I challenge myself to learn without a guide and without the cube itself. I enjoyed mathematics as a young boy and later studied theoretical physics at the Faculty of Mathematics and Physics, where I explored the horizons of black holes. As a theoretical physicist, I realized that understanding the real world makes it easier to navigate any imaginary one, including game worlds. If you want to go from being a user to a creator, the key lies in grasping principles far deeper than you may have ever heard of.\n\n
        Marek Vachal\n
        My journey into fantasy and gaming began when I was six. At fourteen, I encountered Indian philosophy, which shaped my intellectual path. After high school, where I studied bookselling, I continued at the Faculty of Arts, specializing in Indian traditions at the Department of Comparative Study of Religions. Ironically, studying this distant culture led me to delve deeper into Western culture, showing me that the fantasy world can be far more fantastical than one might imagine.\n
    </string>
    <string name="gameRulesText">
        Introduction\n
            Each game represents a single battle and is turn-based. Each round consists of two phases:\n
                1. Fleet movement of both players\n
                2. Fleet encounters\n
            Each fleet consists of spaceships, referred to as units.\n\n

        Units\n
            There are four types of units in the game:\n
                1. Cruiser\n
                    - Firepower: 1\n
                    - Shields: 10\n
                2. Destroyer\n
                    - Firepower: 2\n
                    - Shields: 10\n
                    - Ability: The total firepower of destroyers cannot exceed the number of enemy units on the battlefield.\n
                3. Ghost\n
                    - Firepower: 1\n
                    - Shields: 5\n
                    - Ability: Each Ghost disables one enemy Destroyer. The Destroyer is not destroyed but does not participate in combat as long as the Ghost is alive.\n
                4. Warper\n
                    - Firepower: 2\n
                    - Shields: 1\n
                    - Ability: Can move to any field during the movement phase.\n\n

        Movement\n
            - Each player has a total of 11 units.\n
            - Units move across fields, one field per turn, except for the Warper, which can move anywhere.\n
            - A maximum of 6 units from one player can occupy a single field, so up to 12 units (6 from each player) can be on one field.\n
            - Units on a field controlled by the enemy cannot move to another enemy-controlled field.\n
            - After both players complete their moves, the encounter phase begins.\n\n

        Fleet Encounter\n
            If units from both players are on the same field, a fleet encounter occurs. Encounters proceed in rounds.\n\n

            1. Maximum Tolerable Losses\n
                - When moving fleets, each player sets a \"maximum tolerable loss\" for the encounter. This value represents the number of units the player is willing to lose in the encounter.\n
                - The encounter ends when one player\'s fleet reaches this limit. The player who reaches their tolerable losses loses the encounter.\n\n

            2. Fleet Firepower\n
                - Fleet firepower is the sum of the firepower of all units in the fleet.\n
                - Firepower targets the unit type that is most numerous in the fleet. If there is a tie, the following priority is used:\n
                Cruiser > Destroyer > Ghost > Warper\n\n

            3. Attack\n
                - Each round, the fleet hits the enemy units, dealing damage equal to the fleet\'s firepower.\n
                - Damage is deducted from the unit\’s shields. If a unit loses all its shields, any remaining damage is transferred to the next unit according to the priority.\n
                - Destroyed units no longer contribute to the fleet\'s firepower.\n\n

            4. Firepower Reduction\n
                - Reducing the number of enemy units may decrease the fleet\’s total firepower, especially for Destroyers, whose firepower depends on the number of units on the battlefield.\n\n

        After the Encounter\n
            - After the encounter, all surviving units are restored to their maximum shield values.\n
            - If a player wins the encounter, they gain control of the field. In the case of a draw, the field remains under the control of the original owner.\n\n

        Controlled Field Bonus\n
            - A player who controls a field receives a +1 bonus to firepower in all subsequent encounters on that field.\n\n

        Victory\n
            - Each player begins on their base. If a player loses an encounter on their base field and the opponent gains control of the base, the player loses the game.

    </string>
    <string name="aboutGameText">
        <b>Introduction</b>\n
        What you see today is the first step toward creating an MMORTS set in a future where humanity is capable of space travel. Each player will start with a single home planet and a few spacecraft and begin building their own stellar empire.\n\n

        <b>Current State</b>\n
        In the first phase, we are showcasing only a \“mini-game,\” which will later become part of a large building game and focuses solely on PvP combat. Our goal is to develop this part of our strategy game to the point where it stands on its own as a full-featured experience.\n
        In the game, you will choose the structure of your fleet and attempt to capture your opponent\’s base before they do the same to you. A complete player battle is estimated to last around 10 minutes. It is a turn-based strategy game, where both players plan their move, and once confirmed by both, the plans are executed simultaneously. The game includes different types of ships, each effective in various situations. Its originality lies in a unique decision-making element where players must choose when to strategically retreat or fight to the last ship.\n
        Based on your feedback, we plan to create more developed battle maps and potentially adjust some ship types according to how they are used by real players.\n\n

        <b>Future State</b>\n
        The mini-game presented here will be only a part of a larger building game, starting as an economic game. As the empire grows, it will become increasingly challenging to expand economically, and with greater size, the motivation to expand by force will increase.\n
        Our game will differ from classic online building strategy games in the following ways:\n
        - The game will contain a small number of resources, but they will be realistic commodities. Money will not just be a number generated by gold mines but will adhere to sophisticated, yet player-friendly, economic principles.\n
        - There will be no \“daily tasks\” mechanics forcing you to stay online constantly. We want to design the game so that players can return after any length of time without feeling they missed out on something. The game will encourage you to come back rather than prevent you from leaving.\n
        - The game will contain no \“pay-to-win\” concept at any level.</string>
    <string name="donateText">You can support our efforts with this game on the Buy me a coffee platform. You can choose to support us with a one-time donation or set up a monthly contribution and become a member of our community. Just click the button. We are very grateful for any donation.</string>
    <string name="aiCalculate">Calculating opponent move.</string>
    <string name="waitingForMove">Waiting for opponent move.</string>
    <string name="waitingForOpponent">Waiting for opponent.</string>
    <string name="keepScreenOn">Keep screen on</string>
    <string name="exit" translatable="false">Exit</string>
    <string name="showMap">Show map</string>
    <string name="capitulate">Capitulate</string>
    <string name="capitulateInfoText">Do you really want to capitulate? The game ends and you will lose it.</string>
    <string name="opponentFound">"Opponent have found. Click to start battle. "</string>
    <string name="onlineBattle">Play against human</string>
    <string name="winViaCapitulation">Your opponent capitulated and so you win the game.</string>
    <string name="ok" translatable="false">OK</string>
    <string name="playerTitle">Player info</string>
    <string name="playerInfoText">You play for a %1$s player.</string>
    <string name="redPlayer">red</string>
    <string name="bluePlayer">blue</string>
    <string name="newMessage">New message</string>
    <string name="clickToOpenScreen">Click on this, to open the game.</string>
    <string name="notificationTitleOpponentFound">Opponent has found</string>
    <string name="notificationBodyOpponentFound">Tap to confirm your presence. You must confirm in 1 minute.</string>
    <string name="userEmail" translatable="false">Email</string>
    <string name="displayName">Name</string>
    <string name="logOut" translatable="false">Logout</string>
    <string name="userLogout">No user is login.</string>
    <string name="login" translatable="false">Login</string>
    <string name="userNoEmail">User provide no email.</string>
    <string name="userNoName">User provide no name.</string>
    <string name="signInTitle" translatable="false">Sign in</string>
    <string name="signInAnonymously">Continue as Guest</string>
    <string name="deleteAccount">Delete account</string>
    <string name="deleteAccountText">Are you sure to delete your account? All your data will be delete automatically in 90 days.</string>
    <string name="createAccount">Create account</string>
    <string name="guest">Guest</string>
    <string name="signInText">Play as a guest or sign in via google account to save your progress.</string>


</resources>