<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gravity Game</string>
    <string name="discordInviteLink" translatable="false">https://discord.gg/H4hFa3vgvZ</string>
    <string name="buyMeACoffeeLink" translatable="false">https://buymeacoffee.com/gravitygamp</string>
    <string name="email" translatable="false">gravitygame2024@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="errorToOpenLink">The link can not be open</string>
    <string name="destroyer">Destroyer</string>
    <string name="ghost">Ghost</string>
    <string name="sumArmy">Total units</string>
    <string name="cruiser">Cruiser</string>
    <string name="chooseArmyTitle">Select units to your army</string>
    <string name="exactArmySize">Select maximum units to your army.</string>
    <string name="warper" translatable="false">Warper</string>
    <string name="nameShip">Unit type</string>
    <string name="enemyShips">Enemy units</string>
    <string name="possibleShipsToMove">Your units</string>
    <string name="shipsToMove">Units on position</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="attack">Attack</string>
    <string name="tinyMapName">Tiny map</string>
    <string name="maxLosses">Max losses</string>
    <string name="nextTurn">Next turn</string>
    <string name="cruiserInfo">Firepower: 1\nHit Points: 10\n\nThe basic unit with no extra ability.</string>
    <string name="destroyerInfo">Firepower: 2\nHit points: 10\n\nThe sum of firepower of all your destroyers is maximally as high as the sum of all enemy ships in the battle.</string>
    <string name="ghostInfo">Firepower: 1\nHit points: 5\n\nEvery ghost in the battle excludes one of the enemy destroyers from battle until the ghost is destroyed.</string>
    <string name="warperInfo">Firepower: 2\nHit points: 1\n\nWarper can move to any sector on a battlefield.</string>
    <string name="titleLostGame">You lost the game</string>
    <string name="titleWinGame">You win the game</string>
    <string name="titleDrawGame">The game is draw</string>
    <string name="lostGame">You have fought hard but unfortunately, the opponent has been more lucky.\nYou lost</string>
    <string name="winGame">You have fought hard and well. The opponent has been destroyed.\nYou win. Congratulation</string>
    <string name="drawGame">You and your opponent have fought hard and there is no winner.</string>
    <string name="battleWithAI">Play against AI</string>
    <string name="infoShipTaskTitle">Display unit info</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="numberOfShipsTaskTitle">Number of units in army</string>
    <string name="closeTutorial">Close tutorial</string>
    <string name="acceptableLossesTitle">Acceptable Losses</string>
    <string name="armyDialogSendShipTitle">Attack with units</string>
    <string name="locationLimitTitle">Limit of units</string>
    <string name="timerTaskTitle">Timer</string>
    <string name="movementTaskTitle">Moving with units</string>
    <string name="locationInfoTitle">Display location</string>
    <string name="locationOwnerTitle">Owner of location</string>
    <string name="infoShipTask">Everywhere in the game, you can tap on a unit name to display information about it.</string>
    <string name="numberShipsTask">Now, you are going to choose units for your army for an incoming battle. There are four units types, but one type is unique and you have one unit of the type in your army by default. You can choose from the remaining three units type to 10 units. It means you will fight with an army containing 11 units. When you select your units hit an OK button.</string>
    <string name="battleOverviewTitle">Battle overview</string>
    <string name="battleOverviewTask">Now, the battle starts. When you play against AI, always play for the blue player starting on the left side of the battle map. There is your home planet, where all your units are located. To win a battle you have to conquer an enemy base on his home planet, which is located on the right side of the battle map. On the contrary, when an opponent conquers your base, you lose the battle.</string>
    <string name="movementTask">To move your units tap on a planet where you have at least one unit and move your finger on a planet you want to move your units. When you tap the planet you move from, planets you can move to will be highlighted by green round. At the beginning of the battle, all planets will be highlighted, because your warper can move everywhere, but the rest of your units can move only to adjustment planets. Try it.</string>
    <string name="sendShipsTask">When you select a planet you move from and a planet you move to, you have to select units that will move. The first column displays enemy units on the planet you want to move to, the second column displays your units able to move in this turn on the planet you select to move from. The last column displays the overall number of units on the planet you move to. It means the last column displays units that are already on the planet plus units you choose to move there. You can\'t move an unlimited number of units on a planet. Every planet has a limit of 6 units.</string>
    <string name="acceptableLossesTask">Aside from selecting units, you can also choose how many units you are willing to sacrifice when a battle with an enemy occurs on the planet. You do that by a slider and the number is a number of units. The battle runs in turns where units are firing at each other with their firepower and the battle ends when one army reaches its acceptable losses. When an army reaches this limit units withdraw from the battle. They stand on the planet and next turn you can choose what to do with them. The battle can end with a draw when both armies reach their acceptable losses at the same time.</string>
    <string name="locationInfoTask">You can also check the details of every planet. You can just tap on the planet to open a table, where the numbers of units in both armies are. You can there also change your acceptable losses on that planet any time you want to.</string>
    <string name="locationOwnerTask">Now you can see planets you move to are marked by flag in you color. It shows the planet is yours, which has impact in battle. When you fight on planet you posses your army has 1 firepower higher.</string>
    <string name="gameRulesTitle">Game rules</string>
    <string name="aboutGameTitle">About game</string>
    <string name="aboutUsTitle">About us</string>
    <string name="settingsTitle">Settings</string>
    <string name="selectLanguage">Select language</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="czech">Czech</string>
    <string name="showTutorial">Show tutorial</string>
    <string name="polish">Polish</string>
    <string name="donateTitle" translatable="false">Donate</string>
    <string name="manyShipsOnBaseLocation">There is too many units on your base planet.</string>
    <string name="statisticTitle">Statistics</string>
    <string name="achievementsTitle" translatable="false">Achievements</string>
    <string name="totalBattle">Total battles: %1$s</string>
    <string name="averageTurns">Average turns: %1$s</string>
    <string name="countOfWins">Count of Wins: %1$s</string>
    <string name="countOfLost">Count of Lost: %1$s</string>
    <string name="countOfDraw">Count of Draws: %1$s</string>
    <string name="date" translatable="false">%1$s</string>
    <string name="battleResult">Result: %1$s</string>
    <string name="turns">Turns: %1$s</string>
    <string name="myShipLost">My units lost: %1$s</string>
    <string name="enemyShipDestroyed">Enemy units destroyed: %1$s</string>
    <string name="generalStatistics">General Statistics</string>
    <string name="detailOfBattle">Detail of Battle</string>
    <string name="enemyShipsBeforeBattle">Enemy units before battle</string>
    <string name="enemyShipsLost">Enemy units lost</string>
    <string name="myShipsBeforeBattle">My units before battle</string>
    <string name="myShipsLost">My units lost</string>
    <string name="battleResultOnLocation">"Last battle on the location you %1$s"</string>
    <string name="battleInfoTask">When a battle occur on a planet, you will see an explosion on it. You can long click on the planet to see, how the battle went.</string>
    <string name="battleInfoTaskTitle">Battle info</string>
    <string name="errorToOpenMail">Your email app cannot be open</string>
    <string name="aboutUsText">
        We are two guys for whom games play a significant role in life. We met while playing the now-defunct online strategy game Red Dragon, and we still play various games together today. We enjoy exploring different new mechanisms that are being introduced in the gaming field, and we are not short on ideas ourselves. That’s why we decided to contribute our bit to this field as well. The development of our games always starts with their main mechanism, and as we test it, the game’s theme and any additional secondary mechanisms begin to take shape. Our goal is to bring new and original game mechanisms or unique combinations of existing ones. Last but not least, we aim to offer games that are not burdened by the pay-to-win concept and allow players to play when they want, not when the game dictates. We are people who do not want to be controlled by games, but who choose to play games in their own time.\n\n
        Marek Vachal\n
        My journey into fantasy and games began around the age of six when I started playing Dungeons &amp; Dragons with my father. I have been playing Dungeons &amp; Dragons, other tabletop RPGs, and board games ever since. I also play PC games, primarily building strategies, though less often than before. At the age of 14, I first encountered Indian philosophy, which subsequently shaped my intellectual interests. After high school focusing on bookseller, I enrolled at university in the Department of Comparative Study of Religions, naturally specializing in Indian traditions. Ironically, my study of a foreign culture led me back to exploring Western culture. Today, I can say that our understanding of foreign cultures is still in its early stages. In spite of it, I am already eager to share my insights with the wider public.\n\n
        Marek Basovnik\n
    </string>
    <string name="gameRulesText">
        Movement\n
        - Each player has 11 units. They move units across tiles. All units except the Warper can move one tile per turn.\n
        - A maximum of 6 units per player can occupy a single tile.\n
        - A player cannot move their units onto a tile occupied by the enemy if their units are also on a tile occupied by the enemy.\n
        - A player can move all their units in one turn as long as they meet the condition of having no more than 6 units per tile.\n
        - After both players have completed their moves, the battle phase begins. If both players\' units are on the same tile, a battle ensues.\n\n
        Units\n
        - The three basic units are:\n
        - Cruiser: Firepower: 1, Shields: 10.\n
        - Destroyer: Firepower: 2, Shields: 10. Destroyers in combat can have a combined firepower no greater than the number of the opponent\'s units on the battlefield.\n
        - Ghost: Firepower: 1, Shields: 5. Each Ghost neutralizes one of the opponent\'s Destroyers from combat. The Destroyer is not destroyed but does not participate in the battle as long as the Ghost is alive.\n
        - The unique unit is:\n
        - Warper: Firepower: 2, Shields: 1. In the movement phase, it can move to any tile.\n\n
        Battle\n
        - The battle proceeds in rounds.\n
        - The armies of both players exchange attacks until one player\'s army reaches the "maximum tolerated losses," which is the number of units a player is willing to lose in the battle.\n
        - The army\'s firepower is the sum of the firepower of all units in the army.\n
        - Firepower is always focused on the type of units most represented in the army. In the case of a tie, the target is determined by priority:\n
        - Cruiser > Destroyer > Ghost > Warper\n
        - Each army hits an enemy unit each round, reducing its shields by the amount of its firepower.\n
        - If a unit loses all its shields in a given round, the excess firepower is transferred to the next unit in line according to priority in the same round. A destroyed unit no longer contributes its firepower in subsequent rounds. Similarly, if the number of enemy units decreases, there may be a reduction in firepower for Destroyers due to their firepower limit.\n
        - After a battle, any surviving but damaged units are repaired to their maximum.\n
        - If a player wins the battle on a given tile, they occupy it. In the case of a draw, the tile remains to the original owner.\n
        - On an occupied tile, the player has a +1 firepower bonus in all battles.\n\n
        Victory\n
        Each player has a base. This tile cannot be lost in any way (thus it always has a permanent +1 firepower bonus). If a player loses a battle on his base tile, he lose the game.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutGameText">nn</string>
    <string name="donateText">You can support our efforts with this game on the Buy me a coffee platform. You can choose to support us with a one-time donation or set up a monthly contribution and become a member of our community. Just click the button. We are very grateful for any donation.</string>
</resources>